UNITE Local 23-25 Records 6000/024
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Local 23-25 Records
1982-2012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
UNITE Local 23-25
6000/024
15.33 cubic feet
12.1 linear ft.
Records.
8239553
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 21, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 30, 2015
Scope and Contents
Includes some records of the International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGWU).
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000/024 AV: UNITE Local 23-25 Audio-Visual Materials 6000/024 P: UNITE Local 23-25 Photographs 6000/024 PUBS: UNITE Local 23-25 Publications 6000/024 MB: UNITE Local 23-25 Memorabilia 6000/050: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Files 6000/050 AV: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Audio-Visual Materials 6000/050 MB: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Memorabilia 6000/050 P: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Photographs 6000/050 PUBS: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Publications
Textile industry-- New York (State); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees. Local 23-25 (New York, N.Y.); UNITE HERE (Organization)
8239553
- U.S. Citizenship Lessons, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- H.R. 2202, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- '99-2000 Immigration Muzaffar Chisti, Dir., 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Japanese Labor Magazines, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Chinese News Articles 2002 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Views of Japan, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Asian Labor Items, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Asian Labor Items, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- UNITE!, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO, 1997-2001 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Chinese News, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Workers Center, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Research Article, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Asian Labor Items, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Asian Labor Items, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Garment Initiative Wage & Hour Division, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Chinese New Year, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- '97 Chinese New Year, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- LES Tenement Mus., 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Sweatshops, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- BAO, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- UNITE!, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Immigration 1996 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Garment Industry, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- UNITE Basic Steward Training Manual, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- UNITE Political Directors/Staff Activists conference, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- UNITE! Canadian staff Meeting, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- UNITE! 2000 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Greater Blouse 99-2000, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Union Voice 1997 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- UNITE!, 1998-2012 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Clippings/Releases, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Clippings/Releases, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- UNITE! 1997 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance (APALA), 1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- APALA, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- UNITE!, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Child Health Plus (Box 3, Folder 5)
- UNITE!, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- UNITE!, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Educators for Social Responsibility, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Cornell University Labor Folder, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- UNITE!, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- "Going to work shouldn't be as dangerous as going to war." (Box 3, Folder 11)
- ACTWU Folder, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- 428 B'way Assault, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Politics, Shop Rep Letter, and UNITE!, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Labor Folder, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- China-Labor, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- '96-97 Ela Bhatt, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- CLUW, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- '96 GBA H+S Proposal, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- '95 Beijing Women's Conference, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Guan Baby Case, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Mi La, ZHAO, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Folders, 1996-1998 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- '96 Brooklyn Shop Raids, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- 1997 Press Clips (Box 4, Folder 5)
- '97 Post Office Actions, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Ortiz Hearing 5-29-98, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Museum Talk '96, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Labor Folders, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- '97 H+S Curriculum, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Teacher Training, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Hong Kong - 1997 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Leung, Chui Ha Visit, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- '97 Chinese CLUW, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- 4-15-99 UHC Open Hs., 1999 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Member Assistance Program, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Globalization's Dark Side, 1995-2000 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- 1995 Speeches (Box 5, Folder 2)
- 1996 Speeches (Box 5, Folder 3)
- 1997 Speeches (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Speeches - 2001 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Press Releases 1995 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Press Releases 1996 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Press Releases 1997 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Press Releases 1998 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Press Releases 1999 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Press Releases 2000 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Korean Pamphlets 1996 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- 2000 Women's Center (Box 5, Folder 13)
- National Workplace Literacy Program (Chinatown), 1995 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Education and Training for the Changing Workplace, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Press Prizes, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Subject-Historical-1982-1.23-25 Strike, 1982-1996 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- '95 Apparel Coalition, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Immigration Project, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Ronald Karpman/ N. Stern (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Cohen, Shimon Expense CAF/GIDC 1995 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Memorandum, 1993-1997 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- INS-Certificate of Attorney General Recognition, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- 1059ADD bx 15 UNITE!, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- IRCA Discrimination, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Citizenship, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Miscellaneous Documents, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Department of Labor Compliance Workshops, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- 20th Annual Asian Pacific American Heritage Festival Gift Bag, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Press Clippings (News Stories), 2001 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous UNITE! Papers, 2000-2003 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- New York State Senate and Letters, 1997-2004 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Magazines (Locals) 97-98, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Computer Input (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Executive Board Agenda, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  Scope and Contents
  1 Cassette Tape 11/20/96
- Child Care, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- August 28 - Chinatown, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- UNITE!, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Workers' Center Handbook (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Sol Hoffman Tribute and Asian Documents, 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous Documents, 2001-2007 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- UNITE!, 1998-2004 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Dec. 30 Workshop, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- GEB Minutes '99, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- GEB - Per Capita Report - 2001 & 2002 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Staff Benefits, 1999-2001 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Press Advisory, 1998-2000 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Chinese
- WAR and UNITE!, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- HNY - NYS Insurance Dept., 2005 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Healthy New York 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- GHI Training, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- UNITE HERE Healthy NY EPO, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- 2001 Contractors Health (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Contract on Benefits - 2003, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- SPD Eastern States Fund, 2000-2003 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- May Chen - Petition & GHI Doctor Issues, 1998-2005 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Retiree Awards, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- GEB - 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- May Gen., 1999 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Dec. 2000 GEB, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- "October 2001 GEB" (Box 8, Folder 19)
- July 2001 GEB (Box 8, Folder 20)
- GEB- Montreal, Quebec 9/12/2001 - 9/14/2001 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- February 13-15, 2001 Collective Bargaining Conference (Box 8, Folder 22)
- May 2002 GEB Meeting Montreal, Canada (Box 8, Folder 23)
- GEB - Feb. 18-21st @ Fort Lauderdale, Fl. Also Canada, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- October 2001 GEB Meeting Resolutions (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Convention Resolutions, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- '99 UNITE Convention June 28 - July 1, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Petition to Governor Pataki, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- GIDC 2003 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- GIDC Fundraising of 2000 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- GIDC Linda Dubrak 2002 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Liz C. Grant Day Care 2005 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Day Care By Laws, 1998-2001 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- 2005 Garment Industry Day Care + Scholarships (Box 9, Folder 3)
- 2004 Scholarships (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Scholarship - 2003-2004 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- 2005 Apparel Industry Issues, 2004-2005 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Sourcing Guide 2002 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- '98 Contract - Limited, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Shop Investigation - Organizer's Report, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Classic Couture, 2004-2007 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Elaine L Chao. Vs. Ladies Apparel Group Ltd., 2001 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- 1997 Negotiations (Box 9, Folder 12)
- 2001 Negotiations (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Major Market Negotiations 2001 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Sentry Uniform Cap Co. Inc. July 1, 2005 - June 30, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Marshall Management Employee Benefits Guideline 2003 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- '97 Education Dept., 1997 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Sep. 1, 1999 CLC Rally (Box 9, Folder 18)
- UHC Board Meeting 12/22/98, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- UHC Budget 12/98 Mtg., 1998 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- '96 Labor Day Parade, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- '97 Labor Day Parade, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- '98 Labor Day Parade, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- VC Sportswear, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Day Care 2000 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- '99 Day Care - Gmt., 1999 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- '97 Day Care Bd., 1997 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- 11-2-95 Day Care, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Scholarship Awards 2000 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Scholarship Sponsor By Margie 2000 + Award Ceremony (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Scholarship Information 2000 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- 2000 High School Hist. (Scholarship) (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Renewal Scholarship 2000 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- 2003 Election Committee + Award (Box 10, Folder 6)
- 2003 Renewal (Box 10, Folder 7)
- 2004 Scholarship Award Ceremony (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Scholarship 2002 Renewable Information's (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Guest list 2000 Award (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Unseenamerica Book, 2001-2003 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- UNITE! Second Constitutional Convention, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Translation Material (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Documents, 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- UNITE!, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- '97 Contract, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Backpay Complaint Form, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Sweatshops, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- '98 Jt. Responsibility, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Garment Industry, 1996-2007 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- GIDC Fundraising of 2001 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- UNITE!, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Garment Industry Day Care Center, 1990-1996 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Doc Meeting Notices, 1988-1996 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- GIDC Financial Statement 2004-2005 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Artwork by Michele Sherry Kane/File 2/2001 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Garment Industry Day Care CTR. Fundraising Reception, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Garment Industry Day Care Center, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Day Care Grant - Liz Clairborne Foundation, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- 2004 Day Care Grant Liz Clairborne Foundation (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Union Resources, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Welcome to the UNION! New Members information kit, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- UHC, 1989-1998 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- UNITE Convention 1999 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- NAFTA Scam, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Eastern States Health and Welfare Fund, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Immigration Project, 1985-1994 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Liz Claiborne, 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Immigration Rally 1997 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- UNITE! Asian American, 2001-2003 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Immigration Citizenship, 2001-2003 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Union Health Center (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Current Magazine, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Orientation Package, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- UNITE! Worker Education Program, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- UNITE! New York Worker Education Program Mission Statement, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Mission Statement 1995 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Literally Speaking 1995/96, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- GIDC 1996 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- GIDC 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- GED Application, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- GIDC Schedule, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Retail Campaigns Press Kits, 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Retail Campaigns, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Political Department, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Chinatown, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Standard Report 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- 1998-99 End of the year Reports, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Lisa Johnson (Box 11, Folder 29)
- National Scholarship '97, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- 1997 Award Ceremony (Box 11, Folder 31)
- 1997 Scholarship Committee File (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Questionnaire for Former Winners 1997 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Local 23-25 Scholarship Textbook Program, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Scholar Award 1998 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- 1999 Renewal (Labels) (Box 11, Folder 36)
- 1999 Scholarship Award (Box 11, Folder 37)
  4 Photographs from Event
- Renewal '99, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Student Magazine!, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Cultural Week, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- GEB Convention @ Las Vegas, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- GEB Convention @ Las Vegas, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- GEB, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- 2003 Convention Delegates (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Convention Committee, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- UNITE!, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- 2003 Convention Delegate (Box 12, Folder 9)
- GEB Oct. 7-10, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- GEB Oct. 7-10, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Employees Handbook, 2000-2002 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- GEB Feb 10-13 2003 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- GEB Feb 10-13, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Steward Update (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Agreements, 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- UNITE Immigration Project, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Basic Steward Training Manual (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Meeting Reminder, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Digital Media (Box 12, Folder 20)
  3 Discs
- 23-25 Exec. Board, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- '97 E. Bd. Sign-In's, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- '97 Ex Bd. Payments, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- '97 Ex. Board, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Nov. 20, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 1)